holidaycars.com 2018-08-09

# Privacy Policy - HolidayCars.com

## Privacy Policy

##### Privacy Statement

Your privacy is important to us

##### Privacy Policy

All personal information collected is used only for our purposes as outlined below to improve the services offered to you and similar clients.

##### Security of Information

All sensitive information, including personal details as well as credit card information, is kept confidential through the use of our secure server software (SSL). This means that information can only be exchanged between you and BookingMonkey.com, and that no third party can access this data. The padlock symbol on your browser shows which pages are covered by this security system. BookingMonkey.com uses the GeoTrust True BusinessID Extended Validation certificate which will give you confidence to be able to exchange information in the most secure environment imaginable.

With GeoTrust True BusinessID, based on SSL, the leading security protocol on the Internet, you can rest assured that all information exchanged between you and BookingMonkey.com will be secure during transmission. Please note that our site contains links to other sites. BookingMonkey.com is not responsible for the privacy practices, privacy statements, or content regarding these other sites.

Should you not wish to transmit specific information across the Internet; the contact details shown for BookingMonkey.com will provide alternative ways of providing information. For example, telephone numbers are listed, to enable you to make direct telephone contact with BookingMonkey.com.

##### Data Collected

E-mails and Electronic Forms We will record your e-mail address only if you send us a message. Your personal information will only be used for the purposes for which you have provided it. Your e-mail address will not be added to a mailing list, unless you have provided it to us in order to subscribe to a mailing list we offer.

Where you choose to send us a completed electronic form that includes your personal details, we do collect personally identifiable information, such as name, address and email address and other contact or request details. The information collected by email or electronic forms will be used only for the purpose for which you provided it, and we will not disclose it without your consent, except where authorized or required by law.

##### Browsing

When you browse this web site, the web server records your visit and logs the following information: the user's server address, the user's top level domain name (for example .com, .de, .info, etc), the date and time of visit to the site, the pages accessed and documents viewed, the previous site visited, and the type of browser used.

##### Use of Data Collected

The data listed above is collected for the following purposes: web site and system administration, including monitoring to prevent security breaches enhancement of the web site to our clients' needs and research and development.

#### Use of Cookies

##### Why do we use cookies?

BookingMonkey.com is committed to offering you the best car rental service. To facilitate this, cookies are placed on your computer for us to measure the web surfing behaviors, so that we can tailor our service to you. Cookies are small pieces of information that your browser stores on your computer. When you visit BookingMonkey.com, cookies record information of your online preferences.

##### How do we use cookies?

We collect information about the visits to our website by using Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. The aim is to evaluate the effectiveness of internet advertising on our site and the sites of our partners. Therefore, we make use of cookies placed and delivered by us. We use various advertisement technologies from reputable third parties to gain insight into the behavior of visitors to our website. This is to address certain handlings and transactions of visitors to our website and to identify relevant visitors based on the data of their profiles. When a relevant visitor visits a website within the network of our partners, an advertisement is displayed to the target profile. We monitor the use of our website as well as the servers of our partners. In both cases, the information is collected and maintained via such technologies on our behalf and is not personally identifiable.

##### How can you control cookies?

All your personal data will be kept confidential and will by no means be lent, sold or somehow made public. If you don’t want to receive cookies of BookingMonkey.com, you can modify your browser so that it notifies you when cookies are sent to it or you can refuse cookies altogether. You can also delete cookies that have already been set.

##### Trademark

BookingMonkey Sàrl is a privately owned company; BookingMonkey.com/HolidayCars.com is a registered trademark of BookingMonkey Sàrl. which is registered in the chamber of commerce in Swiss under number CH-550.1.118.325-0.
